Drink with me!
!اشربوا معي
It all started with the idol Fukumoto Miki-chan's commercial.
بدأ كلّ شيء بالإعلان التّجاري للآيدول فوكوموتو ميكي-تشان
I fell in love with Miki-chan and her outfit at first sight.
وقعتُ في حبّ ميكي-تشان وزيّها من النّظرة الأولى
S-So cute...
...ظـ-ظريفة للغاية
So cute! So cute! So cute!
!ظريفة للغاية! ظريفة للغاية! ظريفة للغاية
So when I found a photo from when my mom went to this school,
لذا عندما وجدتُ صورة تعود لأمّي وقتما ،كانت ترتاد هذه المدرسة
I thought it was fate.
ظننتُ بأنّه القدر
If that's where you want to go, that's fine,
،إذا كنتِ تريدين الذّهاب إلى هناك، فلا مشكلة
but it'll be tough.
لكن سيكون ذلك صعباً
I'll work hard!
!سأعمل بجدّ
Also... if I make it into Roubai Academy...
...وأيضاً... إذا التحقتُ بأكاديميّة روباي
I want you to make a sailor uniform for me!
!أريدكِ أن تطرّزي لي زيّ بحّارة رسميّاً
I always admired how my mother looked when she was working.
لطالما أعجبتُ بمظهر أمّي عندما كانت تعمل
I only had eyes for that sailor uniform.
لم أكن أصبو إلّا لزيّ البحّارة الرّسمي ذاك
And that sailor uniform is the reason I got into this school.
وزيّ البحّارة الرّسمي هو السّبب الّذي جعلني ألتحق بهذه المدرسة
The principal said I could wear either uniform, so...
...قالت المُديرة أنّ بمقدوري ارتداء أحد اللّباسين، لذا
I chose the sailor uniform!
!اخترتُ زيّ البحّارة الرّسمي
Episode Two See You Tomorrow
الحلقة الثّانية أراك غداً
Oh, man! I talked for too long!
!يا إلهي! تكلّمتُ لفترة طويلة جدّاً
They're all bored now! I just know it!
!ملَلنَ جميعاً! توقعتُ ذلك
Akebi-san? Are you finished?
أكيبي-سان؟ هل انتهيتِ؟
Oh! My best feature is that my body is really flexible,
،ميزتي المُثلى هي أنّ جسدي مرِن حقّاً
and there's one thing I do that always makes my little sister laugh!
وهناك شيء أفعله دوماً ويُضحِك أختي الصّغيرة
I'd like to finish by showing it to you!
!أريد أن أختتم كلامي باستعراض ذلك لكُن
Here I go!
!ها أنا ذي
After her big sister tries so hard to look awesome...
...بعد أن حاولَتْ أختها الكبرى جاهدة أن تبدو رائعة
I'm a ghost now!
!أنا شبح الآن
This always...
...هذا دائماً
Huh?
ماذا؟
Um... yeah... I'm done now.
المعذرة... أجل... أنتهيتُ الآن
Okay, thank you for that.
حسناً، شكراً لكِ
I understand you a lot better now, Akebi-san.
أفهمكِ بشكل أفضل بكثير الآن يا أكيبي-سان
I thought that last bit was funny, personally.
تلك الجزئيّة الأخيرة كانت مضحكة برأيي
Kizaki-san...
...كيزاكي-سان
Only...
...فقط
I think everyone else...
...أعتقد أنّ الأخريات
well... only saw up your skirt.
بصراحة... رأينَ تنّورتكِ
Washio Hitomi. I plan to join the volleyball club.
واشيو هيتومي. أنوي الانضمام لنادي كُرة الطّائرة
That's all.
هذا كُل ما في الأمر
Seat number 16, Washio Hitomi-san.
رقم المقعد 16، واشيو هيتومي-سان
Volleyball club.
نادي كُرة الطّائرة
She's very tall.
إنّها طويلة جدّاً
16. Washio Hitomi
‏16. واشيو هيتومي
Akebi Komichi
أكيبي كوميتشي
Usagihara Touko
أوساغيهارا توكو
Ohkuma Minoru
أوكوما مينورو
Kamimoku Neko
كاميموكو نيكو
Kizaki Erika
كيزاكي إيريكا
Kojou Tomono
كوجو تومونو
Shijou Riona
شيجو ريونا
Tatsumori Ai
تاتسوموري أي
Tanigawa Kei
تانيغاوا كي
Tougeguchi Ayumi
توغيغوتشي أيومي
Togano Mai
توغانو ماي
Nawashiro Yasuko
ناواشيرو ياسكو
Minakami Riri
ميناكامي ريري
Hiraiwa Hotaru
هيرايوا هوتارو
Hebimori Oshizu
هيبيموري أوشيزو
Washio Hitomi
واشيو هيتومي
Done!
!انتهيت
Well, shall we have lunch now?
حسناً، هل نتناول الغداء الآن؟
Yeah!
!نعم
Okay, move your desks together the way I've drawn on the board to form groups.
حسناً، أزِحن مقاعدكن معاً بالطريقة التي رسمتُها على السبّورة لتشكيل مجموعات
Wh-What do you think?
ما-ما رأيك؟
Yeah, you look great!
!أجل، تبدين رائعة
So do you!
!وكذلك أنتِ
Here you go.
تفضّلي
Thank ya.
شكراً لكِ
She thanked me in a Kansai accent!
!شكرَتْني بلهجة كانساي
Seat number 13, Minakami Riri-san.
المقعد رقم 13، ميناكامي ريري-سان
Here you... go...
...تفضّـ
Seat number 14, Hiraiwa Hotaru-san!
!المقعد رقم 14، هيرايوا هوتارو-سان
How cute!
!ما أظرفها
Careful you don't spill it.
احرصي على ألّا ينسكب منكِ
Thank you.
شكراً لكِ
Akebi-san, if you give everyone that much...
...أكيبي-سان، إذا أعطيتِ الجميع كلّ هذا القدر
Here you go!
!تفضّلي
Yep. See?
نعم. رأيتِ؟
Sitting around our desks like this...
...الجلوس حول مقاعدنا بهذا الشّكل
It feels like we're a family!
!يُشعرنا وكأنّنا عائلة
All right, let's eat.
حسناً، لنأكل
Let's eat.
لنأكل
That's gotta be rough!
!سيكون هذا صعباً
Um, please feel free to use this.
من فضلكِ استخدمي هذه
Oh... Thanks.
شكراً
I left my glasses case in my bag.
تركتُ علبة نظّارتي في حقيبتي
This is a huge help.
هذا يخدمني كثيراً
Glad to hear it!
!يسرّني سماع ذلك
Wait...
...لحظة
Didn't I wipe my sweat with that handkerchief earlier?
ألم أمسح عرَقي بذلك المنديل قبل مدّة؟
Akebi-san?
أكيبي-سان؟
Um, that handkerchief...
...المعذرة، هذا المنديل
Oh, I used the part that's dry.
استخدمتُ الجزء الجافّ
It's fun just watching her.
أتسلّى بمجرّد مشاهدتها
Thanks for the handkerchief, uh...
...شكراً على المنديل
Akebi Komichi!
!أكيبي كوميتشي
Nice to meet you, Kojou Tomono-san!
!سررتُ بلقائكِ يا كوجو تومونو-سان
Nice to meet you. You actually remembered my name.
سررتُ بلقائكِ. تذكّرتِ اسمي في الواقع
I'm so happy.
تغمرني السّعادة
Seat number 6, Kojou Tomono-san.
رقم المقعد 6، كوجو تومونو-سان
She's a really nice girl.
إنّها فتاة لطيفة حقّاً
I bet you're pretty popular, right, Akebi-chan?
أنا متأكّدة بأنّكِ مشهورة جدّاً، أليس كذلك يا أكيبي-تشان؟
Seat number 2, Usagihara Touko-san.
المقعد رقم 2، أوساغيهارا توكو-سان
I've never been popular in my life!
!لم أشتهر هكذا في حياتي
No way! You're the only one in a pure white sailor uniform.
مستحيل! أنتِ الوحيدة بزيّ بحّارة أبيض ناصع
And you wear it so well, too.
وترتدينه بإتقان أيضاً
You're like an idol!
!أنتِ كآيدول
I-Ido...
...آيـ
Y-You can call me that all you want, but I won't do anything for you!
يـ-يمكنكِ أن تصفيني بهذا الشّكل مهما شئتِ، لكن لن أفعل شيئاً لكِ
Kao! She said I look like an idol!
!كاو! قالتْ بأنّني أشبه آيدول
Seriously, your face is just my type, too.
بجدّية، وجهكِ هو نوعي المُفضّل أيضاً
Wow, no one's ever said that to me before!
!مذهل، لم يسبق أن قال أحد ذلك لي
But the blazer looks nice too, doesn't it?
لكن السّترة تبدو لطيفة أيضاً، أليس كذلك؟
I really wanted to wear this.
رغبتُ ارتداءها رغبة شديدة
Yeah! It looks really mature!
!أجل! تبدو ناضجة حقّاً
I wanna wear one someday, too!
!أريد أن أرتدي واحدة أيضاً
Well, then... want to try it on now?
حسناً إذاً... أتريدين تجربتها الآن؟
There we go.
ها أنا ذي
Okay!
!حسناً
Lend me yours, too.
أعيريني زيّكِ أيضاً
Oh, wow! Really?
مذهل! حقّاً؟
Huh?!
!ماذا؟
Whoa! Wait, wait!
!مهلاً! انتظري، انتظري
She was just joking!
!كانت تمزح فحسب
If you take that off, won't you be in just your underwear?
إن خلعتِ هذا، ألن تبقي بلباسكِ الدّاخلي فحسب؟
Oh, right!
!صحيح
Wow, you're the serious type, huh?
عجباً، أنتِ جدّية تماماً
You're just such a smooth talker, I walked right into it.
أنتِ ذكيّة في الإقناع لدرجة أنّني تماشيتُ معكِ
Uh, no, you're just super accident-prone.
لا، أنتِ ميّالة جدّاً للتعرّض للحوادث فحسب
I need to make sure no creepy pests get hold of her.
أريد أن أحرص على ألّا تتواصل معها أي حشرة مُريبة
Cackle, cackle, cackle...
...قهقهة، قهقهة، قهقهة
What?! You didn't go to cram school, Akebi-chan?!
!ماذا؟! لم ترتادي مدرسة الحشو يا أكيبي-تشان؟
That's so unusual!
!هذا أمر غير عاديّ
I-Is that weird?
أ-أهذا غريب إلى تلك الدّرجة؟
No, it's just that almost everyone trying to get into Roubai goes to one.
لا، كلّ ما في الأمر أنّ كلّ تلميذة تحاول الالتحاق بروباي ترتاد مدرسة حشو
For instance...
...على سبيل المثال
That girl there!
!الفتاة التي هناك
Tanigawa Kei. She always scored the highest on mock exams.
تانيغاوا كي. دائماً ما تحرز أعلى العلامات في الامتحانات الصّورية
You can't go wrong having her as a friend.
حاولي ألّا تخطئي وتتّخذينها صديقة
And that's Tatsumori Ai.
وتلك تاتسوموري أي
She went to the same cram school as me.
ارتادت نفس مدرسة الحشو التي ارتدتُها
She's short-tempered and gets mad easily.
إنّها مزاجيّة وسريعة الغضب
She called me out for talking during study periods so many times.
كثيراً ما تستدعيني لنتكلّم أثناء الحصص الدراسيّة
Isn't that your own fault?
أليس هذا ذنبكِ؟
Oh, by the way...
...بالمناسبة
Hi, everyone! This is Mika, second-year, with the broadcasting club!
!مرحباً جميعاً! هذه ميكا، سنة ثانية، من نادي البثّ
You and those two girls you pointed out are from Tokyo, right?
أنتِ ومن أشرتِ إليهما من طوكيو، صحيح؟
Yep.
أجل
I'm Miku.
أنا ميكو
Kizaki-san's also from Tokyo, and Kojou-san is from Nagano.
كيزاكي-سان من طوكيو أيضاً، وكوجو-سان من ناغانو
To all the new first-years, congrats on getting in!
،إلى كافّة تلميذات السنة الأولى الجديدات !تهانينا الالتحاق
Nice to meet you all.
سررتُ بلقائكن جميعاً
How do you all come to school?
كيف تأتَينَ جميعاً إلى المدرسة؟
This program is being broadcast into every classroom from the broadcasting club's station!
!يُبثّ هذا البرنامج إلى كلّ صفّ من محطّة نادي البثّ
Oh, I—
—أنا
You either move here or stay in the dorms!
!إمّا بالانتقال إلى هنا أو الإقامة في الحرَم
The goal is to broadcast all over Japan.
الهدف هو البثّ في كلّ أنحاء اليابان
I'm staying at my grandma's—
—أقيم في منزل جدّتـ
Dorm life for me!
!حياة الحرَم بالنسبة لي
Anyway, it's time for Roubai's hit chart!
!على أيّ حال، حان وقت قائمة أنجح الأغاني بالنسبة لروباي
Also, Kizaki-san's my neighbor!
!وأيضاً كيزاكي-سان جارتي
Huh?
ماذا؟
Really? That's great.
حقّاً؟ هذا رائع
Today, we've got the perfect congratulatory song for you!
!اليوم، لدينا أغنية التّهنئة المثاليّة لكُن
Huh?
ماذا؟
Just for you.
لكُنّ فقط
Dorms, huh? I've always wanted to stay in one.
حرَم؟ لطالما أردتُ الإقامة في أحدهم
Wait, no! It's not perfect! Call me out on that!
!لحظة، لا! ليست مثاليّة! استبعديني منها
Yeah, it's a song about a one-sided crush.
أجل، إنّها أغنية عن حبّ من طرف واحد
Can I come visit you sometime?
هل يمكنكِ المجيء لزيارتكِ في وقت ما؟
Blessings to all high school girls!
!عسى أن تحلّ البركة على كلّ فتيات الثانويّة
As soon as you can!
!في أسرع وقت ممكن
Wait, what?
لحظة، ماذا؟
Blessings to all!
!فلتحلّ البركة على الجميع
Now, please listen to...
...والآن استمعنَ رجاء إلى
Fukumoto Miki's "Delusion."
وهم" لـ فوكوموتو ميكي"
Hey, Akebi-san, you said you liked this singer, right?
أكيبي-سان، قلتِ بأنّكِ تحبّين هذه المغنّية، صحيح؟
Yeah! Miki-chan looks super cute singing this song!
!أجل! تبدو ميكي-تشان ظيفة جدّاً عندما تغنّيها
Yeah? How so?
حقّاً؟ لماذا؟
Well...
...في الحقيقة
Oh, like what she does in this part here!
!مثل ما تفعله في هذه الجزئية هنا
Oh, the thing with the lip balm?
تقصدين بلسم الشّفاه؟
Yeah! You know about it?!
!أجل! تعلمين بأمره؟
I don't. What does she do?
انا لا أعلم. ماذا تفعل؟
Akebi-chan, show her!
!أكيبي-تشان، أريها
I wouldn't get it across very well, though.
لكن لن أتمكّن من تقليدها بنجاح
Nah, you can totally do it!
!لا، يمكنكِ فعلها بإتقان
I even have lip balm right here!
!وحتّى أنّ لديّ بلسم شفاه هنا
Akebi-san...
...أكيبي-سان
If you can't even express what you love most about your favorite...
إن كنتِ حتّى تعجزين عن التّعبير عن ...أكثر ما تحبّينه والمفضّل لديكِ
Can you really call yourself a fan?
فهل يمكنكِ أن تعتبري نفسكِ مُعجبة؟
I-I can do it!
!يـ-يمكنني فعلها
C-Can you?
هـ-هل يمكنك؟
But if I'm going to do it, I have to do it right,
،لكن إذا كنتُ سأفعلها، عليّ فعلها بشكل صحيح
or it'd be an insult to Miki-chan.
وإلّا ستكون إهانة لميكي-تشان
I'll wipe this off before I return it.
سأمسح هذا قبل أن أعيده
Sure, sure.
حسناً، حسناً
She puts lip balm on two fingers like this,
،تضع بلسم الشّفاه على إصبعين هكذا
brings them up to her lips, and...
...ثمّ تقرّبهما من شفتيها و
Akebi-chan, do the thing where you look upward at us again!
أكيبي-تشان، كرّري الجزئيّة الّتي نظرتِ فيها للأعلى نحونا ثانية
Huh? Okay...
...حسناً
Like this?
هكذا؟
Akebi-chan! One more!
!أكيبي-تشان! مرة أخرى
Okay!
!حسناً
Akebi-san! You definitely got her appeal across!
!أكيبي-سان! لقد حفّزتِ رغبتها
Really?
حقّاً؟
Quit making her do it over and over! You're putting her on the spot!
!كفّي عن الطلبِ منها تكرار ذلك !أنتِ تحرجينها بذلك
Uh, uh, I do not speak Japanese.
أنا لا أتكلّم اليابانيّة
Liar! I know you do!
!كاذبة! أعلم بأنّكِ تتكلّمينها
What is this feeling?
ما هذا الشّعور؟
I feel full... in multiple ways.
أشعر بالرّضا... من أكثر من ناحية
Thanks for lunch!
!شكراً على الغداء
There.
هنا
Akebi-chan!
!أكيبي-تشان
What do you wanna play?
ماذا تريدين أن تلعبي؟
Okay, good job!
!حسناً، أحسنتِ صنعاً
Komichi-chan, what do you want to play?
كوميتشي-تشان، ماذا تريدين أن تلعبي؟
It's okay! I'll play by myself!
!لا عليكِ! سألعب بمفردي
Just keep working while you watch me!
!استمرّي في العمل فحسب بينما تراقبينني
I can skip two bars now!
!يمكنني تخطّي قضيبين الآن
How about...
...ما رأيكُن بـ
All that's left is the closing.
كلّ ما بقي هو الإغلاق
So, Tamura-sensei, how was your first day as homeroom teacher?
حسناً يا تامورا-سينسي، كيف كان يومكِ الأوّل كمُعلّمة؟
R-Right!
!حـ-حسناً
I have lots of very unique students.
لديّ كثير من الطّالبات المُميّزات جدّاً
Honestly, I'm a little anxious.
بصراحة، أنا متوتّرة قليلاً
Class Roster
قائمة طالبات الصفّ
But I think it's going to be a fun class.
لكن أعتقد سيكون صفّاً مُثيراً للاهتمام
Akebi Komichi
أكيبي كوميتشي
Akebi-san!
!أكيبي-سان
See you tomorrow.
أراكِ غداً
See ya!
!إلى اللّقاء
Oh... Yeah, see you tomorrow.
أجل، أراكما غداً
She said, "See you tomorrow"!
!"قالت، "أراكِ غداً
I got a little nervous.
توتّرتُ قليلاً
I'll have to say it tomorrow!
!عليّ أن أقولها غداً
Usagihara Touko-san...
...أوساهيغارا توكو-سان
Ohkuma Minoru-san...
...أوكوما مينورو-سان
Kamimoku Neko-san...
...كاميموكو نيكو-سان
Kizaki Erika-san!
!كيزاكي إيريكا-سان
Kojou Tomono-san...
...كوجو تومونو-سان
Shijou Riona-san...
...شيجو ريونا-سان
Tatsumori Ai-san...
...تاتسوموري أي-سان
Tanigawa Kei-san...
...تانيغاوا كي-سان
Tougeguchi Ayumi-san...
...توغيغوتشي أيومي-سان
Togano Mai-san...
...توغانو ماي-سان
Nawashiro Yasuko-san...
...ناواشيرو ياسكو-سان
Minakami Riri-san...
...ميناكامي ريري-سان
Hiraiwa Hotaru-san...
...هيرايوا هوتارو-سان
Hebimori Oshizu-san...
...هيبيموري أوشيزو-سان
Washio Hitomi-san...
...واشيو هيتومي-سان
All of you!
!جميعكن
See you tomorrow!
!أراكُن غداً
I'm home.
عُدت
Welcome back. Your dad's home.
أهلاً بعودتكِ. أبوكِ في المنزل
He says he has to go back to work tomorrow morning.
يقال بأنّه عليه العودة للعمل في صباح الغد
He asked where you were.
سأل عنكِ
He wanted to see you in your sailor uniform.
أراد رؤيتكِ بزيّ البحّارة الرّسمي
Should I wait a bit before changing?
هل أنتظر قليلاً قبل تبديل ملابسي؟
Oh, it's fine. His own fault for falling asleep.
لا مشكلة. هذه غلطته لأنّه غطّ في النّوم
Besides, you probably ran and got all sweaty, right?
فضلاً عن ذلك، تعرّقتِ كثيراً غالباً، صحيح؟
Let your uniform dry out a bit first.
جفّفي زيّكِ في الخارج قليلاً أوّلاً
Okay...
...حسناً
Komichi Kao
كوميتشي كاو
Dad? You should sleep in the bed, or you'll get sick.
أبي؟ ينبغي أن تنام في السّرير، وإلّا مرضت
I keep telling him that, but he won't listen.
أقول له ذلك باستمرار، لكنّه لا يصغي إليّ
Come on, Kao. You, too.
هيّا يا كاو. أنتِ أيضاً
Onee-chan...
...أونيه-تشان
Dad came home.
عاد أبي للمنزل
Uh-huh.
أجل
The bath's ready, you two. Go on and get in.
الحمّام جاهز. ادخلا واستحمّا
Okay!
!حسناً
Bathy, bathy, bathy, bathy, bathy time.
وقت الحمّام، وقت الحمّام، وقت الحمّام
You're awake.
استيقظت
You got me.
كشفتِني
I didn't hear any snoring.
لم أسمع أيّ شخير
Well, it's been so long, I got a little nervous.
في الواقع، مضى وقت طويل، لذا توتّرتُ قليلاً
So you faked being asleep? Unbelievable.
فتظاهرتَ بالنّوم؟ غير معقول
Komichi was dying to show off her uniform to you.
كانت كوميتشي مُستميتة لتراها بزيّها الرّسمي
I just don't know what to say to a girl her age that would make her happy.
لا أعرف ما أقول لفتاة في سنّها كلاماً يُسعدها
Komichi's grown up, huh?
نضجَتْ كوميتشي، صحيح؟
Kao, one of the girls in class today said I was funny!
كاو، قالت إحدى الفتيات في الصفّ !اليوم بأنّني طريفة
One even said I looked like an idol!
!وحتّى أنّ إحداهنّ قالت بأنّني كآيدول
You sound like you're enjoying yourself.
يبدو أنّكِ تستمتعين بوقتكِ يا أونيه-تشان
Huh? You think so?
أوتظنّين ذلك؟
I wanna go to that school, too.
أريد الذّهاب إلى تلك المدرسة أيضاً
That'd be great.
سيكون هذا رائعاً
And then I'll wear the same uniform as you!
!ثمّ سأرتدي نفس زيّكِ الرّسميّ
Uh... It's really embarrassing, though.
لكن هذا محرج حقّاً
I'd show it off with pride!
!سأتباهى به بكلّ فخر
You're such a strong girl!
!يا لكِ من فتاة قويّة
Pride, huh?
فخر؟
I bet Kizaki-san couldn't do that.
أنا واثقة بأنّ كيزاكي-سان لا تستطيع فعل ذلك
Who's Kizaki-san?
من كيزاكي-سان؟
My classmate. The one who said I was funny.
زميلة في صفّي. مَن قالت بأنّني طريفة
I wanna meet her!
!أريد لقاءها
You mean you want me to invite her over?
تقصدين أنّكِ تريدينني أن أدعوها إلى منزلنا؟
Yeah! Do it!
!أجل! افعلي ذلك
Oh, no, I couldn't!
!لا، لا أستطيع
Why not?
لمَ لا؟
You think she'd come?
أتعتقدين بأنّها ستأتي؟
Uh-huh. You can tell her Kao said so.
أجل. يمكنكِ أن تخبريها بأنّ كاو قالت ذلك
Darn it, Kao! You're such a good little sister!
!يا إلهي يا كاو! أنتِ أخت صغيرة لطيفة
Okay, then... just a little.
حسناً إذاً... قليلاً فقط
Huh?
ماذا؟
Where's Dad?
أين أبي؟
Dad, welcome home.
أبي، أهلاً بعودتك
Oh, same to you, Komichi.
أنتِ كذلك يا كوميتشي
Thanks.
شكراً
So... how was school?
حسناً... كيف كانت المدرسة؟
I was kinda nervous...
...كنتُ متوتّرة بعض الشيء
But it was fun.
لكن كان ذلك ممتعاً
That so?
حقّاً؟
Yeah.
أجل
Oh, and there's a bunch of stuff I want to tell you!
!وهناك أشياء كثيرة أريد أن أخبرك بها
Komichi...
...كوميتشي
What time are you leaving for school in the morning?
في أيّ ساعة تغادرين إلى المدرسة صباحاً؟
What about you?
ماذا عنك؟
Well... I'll have to be out of here by six.
في الواقع... سأخرج من هنا على السّادسة
Then I'll get changed before that.
إذاً سأبدّل ملابسي قبل ذلك
Can't wait to see it.
أنا متحمّس لرؤيته
Yep!
!أجل
Dad!
!أبي
See you tomorrow!
!أراك غداً